let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The average age of a man and his son is 28 years. The ratio of their ages is 3 :1 respectively. What is the man's age?",
    answer: "42 years",
    options: [
      "30 years",
      "38 years",
      "44 years",
      "42 years"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 2,
    question: "A cyclic quadrilateral ABCD is such that AB = BC, AD = DC, AC is perpendicular to BD and ∠CAD = θ, then find the ∠ABC.",
    answer: "2θ",
    options: [
      "θ",
      "θ/2",
      "2θ",
      "3θ"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: "If tan θ + cot θ = 2, then the value of tan2θ + cot2θ is",
      answer: "2",
      options: [
        "2",
        "1",
        "√2",
        "θ"
      ]
    },
    {
     numb: 4,
        question: "How many integers are there between 300 and 600 that are divisible by 9?",
        answer: "33",
        options: [
        "33",
        "31",
        "28",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
           question: "What will be the ratio of petrol and kerosene in the final solution formed by mixing petrol and kerosene that are present in three identical vessels in the ratio 4:1,5:2 and 6 :1 respectively?",
           answer: "83 : 22",
           options: [
           "166 : 22",
           "83 : 22",
           "83 : 44",
           "78 : 55"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 6,
           question: "The respective ratio of radii of two right circular cylinders (A & B) is 2 : 5. The respective ratio of the heights of cylinders A and B is 3 : 1. What is the respective ratio of volumes of cylinders A and B?",
           answer: "12 : 25",
           options: [
           "12 : 25",
           "9 : 25",
           "9 : 20",
           "3 : 5"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 7,
           question: "Raja gives 30% of his salary to his mother, 40% of the remaining salary he invests in an insurance scheme and PPF in the respective ratio of 4 : 3 and the remaining he keeps in his bank account. If the difference between the amount he gives to his mother and that he invests in insurance scheme is Rs. 8400, how much is Raja’s salary?",
           answer: "Rs. 60,000",
           options: [
           "Rs. 60,000",
           "Rs. 64,000",
           " Rs. 65,000",
           "Rs. 54,000"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 8,
           question: "A, B, C and D are four consecutive odd numbers and their average is 42. What is the product of B and D?",
           answer: "1845",
           options: [
           "1860",
           "1890",
           "1845",
           "1677"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 9,
           question: "A basket contains 3 blue, 5 black and 3 red balls. If 2 balls are drawn at random, what is the probability that one is black and one is red?",
           answer: "3/11",
           options: [
           "2/11",
           "8/11",
           "9/11",
           "3/11"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 10,
           question: "A man buys a land and gives for it 20 times the annual rent Find the rate of interest he gets for his money.",
           answer: "24%",
           options: [
           "10%",
           "24%",
           "45%",
           "18%"
         ]
       },
];